<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>AppleInsider - Frontpage News</title>
    <link>http://appleinsider.com</link>
    <description>AppleInsider News</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 20:03:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Apple reportedly plans high-res 5.5" iPhone 6, all new 4.7" model for later this year</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-reportedly-plans-high-res-55-iphone-6-all-new-47-model-for-later-this-year</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple will release two new iPhones this year, with an all-new redesigned 4.7-inch model and high-resolution &quot;phablet&quot; type 5.5-inch version poised to take the high-end smartphone world by storm this fall.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-reportedly-plans-high-res-55-iphone-6-all-new-47-model-for-later-this-year</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 19:53:01 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple 'likely' to launch low-cost iMac soon, Retina MacBook Air still on track for 2014 debut</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-likely-to-launch-low-cost-imac-soon-retina-macbook-air-still-on-track-for-2014-debut</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple is reportedly gearing up to launch a new low-cost iMac as soon as this quarter, while a completely redesigned thinner and lighter 12-inch MacBook Air with Retina display is expected to launch before the end of the year.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-likely-to-launch-low-cost-imac-soon-retina-macbook-air-still-on-track-for-2014-debut</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 19:46:58 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple to sell two sizes of iWatch with flexible AMOLED displays this fall, prices to reach 'thousands of dollars'</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-to-sell-two-sizes-of-iwatch-with-flexible-amoled-displays-this-fall</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With Apple expected to be fielding a smartwatch later this year, one analyst reveals new details about the long-awaited device, including biometrics, flexible AMOLED display with sapphire cover lens and NFC, among other features.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-to-sell-two-sizes-of-iwatch-with-flexible-amoled-displays-this-fall</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 19:09:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple to roll out glut of new products in Q3 including iWatch in two sizes, 'iPhone 6,' 12" MacBook and low-cost iMac</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-to-roll-out-glut-of-new-products-in-q3-including-iwatch-in-two-sizes-all-new-iphones-starting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to start rolling out new products starting in the second quarter, says one informed analyst, including the much rumored iWatch, redesigned &quot;iPhone 6,&quot; a 12-inch MacBook Air and a low-cost iMac.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-to-roll-out-glut-of-new-products-in-q3-including-iwatch-in-two-sizes-all-new-iphones-starting</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 18:36:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple issues sixth OS X 10.9.3 Mavericks seed to developers with minor tweaks</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-issues-sixth-os-x-1093-mavericks-seed-to-developers-with-minor-tweaks-</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple on Wednesday released to developers the latest version of its upcoming OS X maintenance update, asking beta testers to concentrate on graphics drivers, audio, Safari and iTunes contacts and calendar syncing over USB.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-issues-sixth-os-x-1093-mavericks-seed-to-developers-with-minor-tweaks-</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 18:15:59 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac sales slump in Q1 as PC market faces 8th straight quarterly decline</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/mac-sales-slump-in-q1-as-pc-market-faces-8th-straight-quarterly-decline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple's share of the U.S. computer hardware market slipped during the first quarter of 2014, with both IDC and Gartner seeing a year-over-year decline in worldwide PC shipments as consumers trend toward mobile.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/mac-sales-slump-in-q1-as-pc-market-faces-8th-straight-quarterly-decline</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 16:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB brings RBI Baseball back with iOS app, Cyber Dust aims to be Snapchat for texts</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/mlb-brings-rbi-baseball-back-with-ios-app-cyber-dust-aims-to-be-snapchat-for-texts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[iPhone and iPad owners have new options for fun and communication after Major League Baseball released R.B.I. Baseball for Apple's mobile devices and Dallas Mavericks owner Mark Cuban brought his Snapchat-like test messaging service out of beta.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/mlb-brings-rbi-baseball-back-with-ios-app-cyber-dust-aims-to-be-snapchat-for-texts</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 16:09:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Apple UI chief Greg Christie set to leave after clashes with Jony Ive [update: confirmed]</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/rumor-apple-ui-chief-greg-christie-set-to-leave-after-clashes-with-jony-ive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Longtime Apple human interface director Greg Christie, who has been with the iPhone maker since 1996, is said to be planning an exit after his relationship with recently-elevated senior vice president of design Jony Ive allegedly turned sour.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/rumor-apple-ui-chief-greg-christie-set-to-leave-after-clashes-with-jony-ive</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 15:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple considering 'dramatic' overhaul of iTunes Music Store to boost sales - report</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-considering-dramatic-overhaul-of-itunes-music-store-to-boost-sales---report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facing significant declines in digital music sales, Apple is reportedly plotting a potential overhaul of its iTunes Music Store, in addition to considering new revenue opportunities through on-demand streaming and even allegedly an iTunes for Android.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-considering-dramatic-overhaul-of-itunes-music-store-to-boost-sales---report</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 15:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropbox bringing Mailbox to the Mac, launches new Carousel photo app</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/dropbox-bringing-mailbox-to-the-mac-launches-new-carousel-photo-app</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Popular file synchronization service Dropbox unveiled two new updates for the Apple ecosystem Wednesday, announcing that it would bring its Mailbox e-mail app from iOS to the Mac and showing off a new multimedia gallery app dubbed Carousel.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/dropbox-bringing-mailbox-to-the-mac-launches-new-carousel-photo-app</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 14:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAB 2014 roundup: Thunderbolt 2 accessories, DJI Phantom 2 Vision+, 4K video</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/nab-2014-roundup-thunderbolt-2-accessories-dji-phantom-2-vision-4k-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week is the annual National Association of Broadcasters show, where a number of Mac and iOS compatible products geared toward professionals have been unveiled, including new Thunderbolt 2 accessories, an upgraded DJI Phantom 2 Vision+ flying camera drone, and a plethora of 4K video recording and playing devices.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/nab-2014-roundup-thunderbolt-2-accessories-dji-phantom-2-vision-4k-video</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 12:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple nabs senior RF engineers from Broadcom amid rumors of new in-house baseband team</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-nabs-senior-rf-engineers-from-broadcom-amid-rumors-of-new-in-house-baseband-team</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At least two high-level baseband hardware engineers have left wireless semiconductor company Broadcom for new positions at Apple this year, adding weight to speculation that the iPhone maker is planning to design and build its own baseband processors.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-nabs-senior-rf-engineers-from-broadcom-amid-rumors-of-new-in-house-baseband-team</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 10:40:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple 'considered' buying mobile payment firm Square, but Google deal seen as more likely</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-considered-buying-mobile-payment-firm-square-but-google-deal-seen-as-more-likely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Both Apple and Google have reportedly had internal discussions about making respective offers to buy mobile payment company Square, though Google is seen as the more likely of the two to actually go through with a purchase.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-considered-buying-mobile-payment-firm-square-but-google-deal-seen-as-more-likely</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 09:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's iBeacon tech to be featured at Coachella music and arts festival</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apples-ibeacon-tech-to-be-featured-at-coachella-music-and-arts-festival</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to an app update for the upcoming Coachella Valley Music and Arts Festival, the gathering will have on-site iBeacons that push notifications and other information to users as they walk the grounds at the Empire Polo Club in Indio, Calif. this weekend next.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apples-ibeacon-tech-to-be-featured-at-coachella-music-and-arts-festival</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 03:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Apple takes delivery of iWatch circuit boards ahead of September debut</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/rumor-apple-takes-delivery-of-iwatch-circuit-boards-ahead-of-september-debut</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coming on the heels of a separate iWatch report, sources from the Far East on Wednesday claim Apple has taken receipt of flexible PCB sample boards bound for the much rumored device that could be revealed as soon as September.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/rumor-apple-takes-delivery-of-iwatch-circuit-boards-ahead-of-september-debut</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 01:54:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple moves to renew FRAND licensing suit against Motorola</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-moves-to-renew-frand-licensing-suit-against-motorola-</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a court battle against Samsung raging on the West Coast, Apple on Tuesday asked the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit in Washington, D.C. to renew a lawsuit against Motorola's alleged unreasonable licensing fees for declared-essential cellphone technology.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/09/apple-moves-to-renew-frand-licensing-suit-against-motorola-</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple explains $2.2B damages claim against Samsung from lost profits, royalties</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/apple-explains-full-22b-damages-against-samsung-come-from-lost-profits-royalties</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During testimony in the second California Apple v. Samsung patent trial on Tuesday, an Apple damages expert revealed the full damages claim stands at $2.19 billion for lost profits and reasonable royalty fees on five alleged infringed patents.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/apple-explains-full-22b-damages-against-samsung-come-from-lost-profits-royalties</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 19:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen interest in 'iWatch' growing as iPhone dominates field, study says</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/teen-interest-in-iwatch-growing-as-iphone-dominates-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple's iPhone continues to lead all competing devices in the important U.S. teen demographic, but the future spenders of America are exhibiting fast-growing interest in new product categories like the iWatch.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/teen-interest-in-iwatch-growing-as-iphone-dominates-field</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 17:08:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP Morgan sees Apple further eating away at Windows PC market with sub-$1000 iOS notebook</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/jp-morgan-sees-apple-further-eating-away-at-windows-pc-market-with-sub-1000-ios-notebook</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple is excluding itself from a $63 billion market opportunity, investment firm J.P. Morgan believes, by only partially competing in the sub-$1,000 portable computing market, which is why one analyst argues Apple should introduce a new notebook powered by a more full-featured version of iOS.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/jp-morgan-sees-apple-further-eating-away-at-windows-pc-market-with-sub-1000-ios-notebook</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 14:52:38 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'mApp' platform helps museums leverage Apple's iBeacons for interactive exhibits</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/new-mapp-platform-helps-museums-leverage-apples-ibeacons-for-interactive-exhibits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Museum visits may become far more immersive in the future thanks to Dutch microlocation startup LabWerk's new mApp platform, a deployment and management system that allows museums to quickly and easily roll out iBeacon-based interactive exhibits.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/new-mapp-platform-helps-museums-leverage-apples-ibeacons-for-interactive-exhibits</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 14:28:07 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In pushing for Time Warner merger, Comcast cites Apple's development of new set-top box</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/in-pushing-for-time-warner-merger-comcast-cites-apples-development-of-new-set-top-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rumors that Apple is working on a new set-top box are high-profile enough that Comcast saw it fit to cite them on Tuesday as part of a filing with the U.S. Federal Communications Commission.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/in-pushing-for-time-warner-merger-comcast-cites-apples-development-of-new-set-top-box</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 12:29:39 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile malware authors 'almost exclusively' focused on Android in 2013, says Symantec</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/mobile-malware-authors-almost-exclusively-focused-on-android-in-2013-says-symantec</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attackers continue to target Android more than any other mobile operating system, according to a new report released Tuesday, as Google's platform played host to all but one of the new mobile malware families discovered last year.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/mobile-malware-authors-almost-exclusively-focused-on-android-in-2013-says-symantec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 12:06:08 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft hopes to counter Apple with AI-driven 'invisible user interfaces' on future devices</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/microsoft-hopes-to-counter-apple-with-ai-driven-invisible-user-interfaces-on-future-devices</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Just days after officially announcing Cortana, a Siri-like personal digital assistant for Windows Phone, Microsoft has revealed a substantial and wide-ranging artificial intelligence program it hopes will leapfrog similar offerings from Apple and Google.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/microsoft-hopes-to-counter-apple-with-ai-driven-invisible-user-interfaces-on-future-devices</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 09:53:04 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple, Google &amp; others could pay 'blindingly high' $9B in anti-poaching class-action suit</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/apple-google-others-could-pay-blindingly-high-9b-in-anti-poaching-class-action-suit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A class-action lawsuit from tech sector employees against employers including Apple and Google seeks some $9 billion in lost wages --?an astronomical sum that the complainants could ultimately receive, some believe, thanks to a mountain of evidence appearing to implicate Silicon Valley employers in an alleged no-hire cartel.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/apple-google-others-could-pay-blindingly-high-9b-in-anti-poaching-class-action-suit</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 09:09:29 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Quanta to build 65M Apple "iWatch" units in first year, Q3 2014 release expected</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/rumor-quanta-to-build-65m-apple-iwatch-units-in-first-year-q3-2014-release-expected</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A suspect new report out of China claims to have a great deal of specifics on Apple's rumored &quot;iWatch,&quot; namely that it will debut in the third quarter of this year and will include advanced sensors to detect a user's heart rate and blood pressure, among other things.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/rumor-quanta-to-build-65m-apple-iwatch-units-in-first-year-q3-2014-release-expected</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 07:34:19 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Apple plans to bring iPhone baseband chip design in-house</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/rumor-apple-plans-to-bring-baseband-chip-design-in-house</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A rumor from the Far East on Tuesday claims Apple is mulling the creation of a research and development team that will be responsible for designing future iPhone baseband processors to be used as soon as 2015.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/rumor-apple-plans-to-bring-baseband-chip-design-in-house</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 02:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe's 'Lightroom mobile' for iPad brings advanced photo editing, organization to iOS</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/adobes-lightroom-mobile-for-ipad-brings-advanced-photo-editing-organization-to-ios</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adobe on Monday introduced Lightroom Mobile for iPad, a touch-friendly accompaniment to the company's suite of photography software that brings powerful new tools to Apple's iOS, including on-the-go RAW image editing.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/08/adobes-lightroom-mobile-for-ipad-brings-advanced-photo-editing-organization-to-ios</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 01:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays: Apple's 'iWatch' could include UV light exposure sensor</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/barclays-apples-iwatch-could-include-uv-light-exposure-sensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple might be looking to lend a helping hand to those who are particularly prone to sunburns or are otherwise sensitive to harmful UV rays, as one analyst believes that the company will include new UV exposure sensors in its so-called &quot;iWatch.&quot;]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/barclays-apples-iwatch-could-include-uv-light-exposure-sensor</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 22:52:56 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung sues newspaper for $284k over negative reports on Galaxy S5</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/samsung-sues-newspaper-for-284k-over-negative-reports-on-galaxy-s5</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Samsung has sued Electronic Times for 300 million KRW (about $284,000 US) regarding its reporting related to the company's new Galaxy S5 phone.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/samsung-sues-newspaper-for-284k-over-negative-reports-on-galaxy-s5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 21:26:30 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple sends out WWDC 2014 ticket purchase invitations to randomly selected developers</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/apple-sends-out-invitations-to-buy-wwdc-2014-tickets-after-random-selection-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple on Monday sent out emails to developers who participated in this year's WWDC 2014 ticket lottery, notifying those accepted that tickets will be saved until Apr. 14.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/apple-sends-out-invitations-to-buy-wwdc-2014-tickets-after-random-selection-process</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 20:37:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's Schiller was 'shocked' at ad agency's suggestions for branding turnaround, documents show</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/apples-schiller-was-shocked-at-ad-agencys-suggestions-for-branding-turnaround-documents-show</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Email correspondence made public as part of the second California Apple v. Samsung patent trial illustrates Apple marketing guru Phil Schiller's displeasure at the company's high-profile ad agency, which in 2013 was under the gun to churn out quality material in light of Samsung's own media blitz.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/apples-schiller-was-shocked-at-ad-agencys-suggestions-for-branding-turnaround-documents-show</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 19:33:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's iOS 7 reaches 87% adoption, still growing faster than Android 4.4 KitKat</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/apples-ios-7-reaches-87-adoption-still-growing-faster-than-android-44-kitkat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple has updated its App Store statistics for April, reporting that 87 percent of its users accessing the iTunes Store have now installed its latest iOS 7.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/apples-ios-7-reaches-87-adoption-still-growing-faster-than-android-44-kitkat</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 17:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bollywood choreographer subject of latest 'Your Verse' story in iPad ad campaign</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/bollywood-choreographer-subject-of-latest-your-verse-story-in-ipad-ad-campaign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple on Monday posted to its website the latest installment of its &quot;Your Verse&quot; ad campaign, this time focusing on Bollywood choreographer Feroz Khan and his the day-to-day with the iPad Air.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/bollywood-choreographer-subject-of-latest-your-verse-story-in-ipad-ad-campaign</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 17:02:27 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel unveils 10-gigabit Ethernet Thunderbolt Networking coming to Macs, PCs</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/intel-unveils-10-gigabit-ethernet-thunderbolt-networking-coming-to-macs-pcs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intel on Monday took the covers off of Thunderbolt Networking, an addition to the Thunderbolt 2 interconnect standard that will allow users to transfer data between two Macs and PCs at up to 10 gigabits per second over an emulated Ethernet connection.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/intel-unveils-10-gigabit-ethernet-thunderbolt-networking-coming-to-macs-pcs</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 13:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply chain data suggests Apple's March quarter could be stronger than Wall Street expects</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/supply-chain-data-suggests-apples-march-quarter-could-be-stronger-than-wall-street-expects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sales data from some of Apple's biggest suppliers shows stronger than expected returns for the just-concluded month of March, potentially hinting that Apple itself could also surprise to the upside when it reports earnings later this month.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/supply-chain-data-suggests-apples-march-quarter-could-be-stronger-than-wall-street-expects</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 13:03:51 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: Amazon's Fire TV makes iterative improvements in set-top streaming</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/review-amazons-fire-tv-makes-iterative-improvements-in-set-top-streaming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The set-top streaming business got a little more crowded when Amazon announced the Fire TV last week. With voice-activated search, predictive content loading and a gaming &quot;bonus feature,&quot; the Internet retail giant is positioning its new device as a cure-all usability for problems plaguing existing products.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/review-amazons-fire-tv-makes-iterative-improvements-in-set-top-streaming</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 09:55:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft shows off new 'Windows in the car' concept to take on Apple's CarPlay</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/microsoft-shows-off-new-windows-in-the-car-concept-to-take-on-apples-carplay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Software giant Microsoft is planning to revamp its in-car offerings after suffering setbacks with the existing Sync platform, unveiling a new &quot;Windows in the car&quot; initiative at the company's annual Build conference in San Francisco.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/microsoft-shows-off-new-windows-in-the-car-concept-to-take-on-apples-carplay</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 09:31:56 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's 'Beat Apple' memo: 'Threat from Apple extremely real and urgent'</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/samsungs-beat-apple-memo-threat-from-apple-extremely-real-and-urgent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the tech media has devoted lots of attention to Apple's concerned reaction to Samsung's 2012 marketing blitz, evidence likely to be presented during the Apple vs Samsung trial shows that it was Samsung that targeted its attention on &quot;beating Apple&quot; as its &quot;#1 priority&quot; for 2012.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/07/samsungs-beat-apple-memo-threat-from-apple-extremely-real-and-urgent</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 05:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: Parrot's AR.Drone 2.0 makes iPhone aerial reconnaissance easy</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/06/review-parrots-ardrone-20-makes-iphone-aerial-reconnaissance-easy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As one of the most popular iOS-friendly aerial camera platforms available, Parrot's AR.Drone has become a great example of what's possible within Apple's mobile ecosystem. AppleInsider was recently able to spend time with the second-generation version to see if it's worth the $300 price of entry.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/06/review-parrots-ardrone-20-makes-iphone-aerial-reconnaissance-easy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 06:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google prepping 'Android TV' set-top box with stripped-down interface, voice input and notifications</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/05/google-prepping-android-tv-set-top-box-with-stripped-down-interface-voice-input-and-notifications</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to supposedly leaked documents, Google is readying a new contender for the living room in Android TV, a set-top box with an easy-to-use card interface, voice controls, push notifications and more.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/05/google-prepping-android-tv-set-top-box-with-stripped-down-interface-voice-input-and-notifications</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 19:57:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple unlocks new Copy Cat docs as evidence Samsung pilfered iPhone unlock</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/05/apple-unlocks-new-copy-cat-docs-as-evidence-samsung-pilfered-iphone-unlock</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the original Apple vs Samsung patent trial, Apple made the Galaxy a star witness by presenting a &quot;copy cat&quot; document that detailed every difference with Apple's iPhone paired with advice on how to more closely copy it. For the second trial, Apple has dug up several more Copy Cat docs detailing the evolution of Samsung's &quot;slavish copying,&quot; particularly evident with Slide to Unlock.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/05/apple-unlocks-new-copy-cat-docs-as-evidence-samsung-pilfered-iphone-unlock</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 17:43:47 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email from Steve Jobs reveals Apple TV 'magic wand,' other future product ideas</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/email-from-steve-jobs-reveals-rare-look-at-internal-apple-strategy-meeting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An email Apple cofounder Steve Jobs sent to his top executives outlines the vision he had for the company in 2010, including future iPhone iterations, &quot;Apple TV 2&quot; and changes to MobileMe that hoped would leapfrog Google's cloud services.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/email-from-steve-jobs-reveals-rare-look-at-internal-apple-strategy-meeting</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 21:44:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple initially wanted original iPhone to be 'always on' device but opted for 'slide-to-unlock'</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/apple-initially-wanted-original-iphone-to-be-always-on-device-but-opted-for-slide-to-unlock</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the Apple v. Samsung patent trial on Friday, Apple software engineer and head of the company's human interface team Greg Christie took the stand to offer background on the original iPhone, specifically the &quot;slide-to-unlock&quot; feature.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/apple-initially-wanted-original-iphone-to-be-always-on-device-but-opted-for-slide-to-unlock</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 19:51:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After outing business dealings with Apple, Pixelworks appoints ex-Apple exec to board</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/after-outing-business-dealings-with-apple-pixelworks-appoints-ex-apple-exec-to-board</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-resolution display processing company Pixelworks on Friday announced the appointment of ex-iPod and iPhone hardware executive David J. Tupman to its board of directors, with the news coming one month after the firm revealed Apple orders accounted for ten percent of its business in 2013.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/after-outing-business-dealings-with-apple-pixelworks-appoints-ex-apple-exec-to-board</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 18:55:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple sales team concerned about shrinking high-end iPhone market, but Schiller disagrees</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/apple-sales-team-concerned-about-shrinking-high-end-iphone-market-but-schiller-disagrees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An internal Apple document presented as part of the ongoing Samsung v. Apple trial shows that the company's sales team was worried that a maturing market may leave no room for iPhone growth, though marketing chief Phil Schiller downplayed the document's significance.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/apple-sales-team-concerned-about-shrinking-high-end-iphone-market-but-schiller-disagrees</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 15:10:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's Tim Cook banked $74M in 2013, topping all but one S&amp;P 500 tech CEO</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/apples-tim-cook-banked-74m-in-2013-topping-all-but-one-sp-500-tech-ceo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple Chief Executive Tim Cook took home $4.3 million in salary and incentives in 2013 and added another $69.6 million in vested stock options, continuing his reign as one of the highest-paid executives in Silicon Valley.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/apples-tim-cook-banked-74m-in-2013-topping-all-but-one-sp-500-tech-ceo</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 14:39:28 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's (RED) contributions in fight against AIDS reach $70 million</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/apples-red-contributions-in-fight-against-aids-reach-70-million</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple's contributions to (RED), which aims to eliminate HIV and AIDS, have now reached $70 million to date, the charity officially announced on Friday.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/apples-red-contributions-in-fight-against-aids-reach-70-million</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 13:32:27 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixar president recalls a 'transformation' undergone by Apple co-founder Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/pixar-president-recalls-a-transformation-undergone-by-apple-co-founder-steve-jobs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Steve Jobs is famous for helping to turn Pixar into a legendary award winning animation studio, the experience of running Pixar also helped to change Jobs himself for the better, the studio's president reveals in a new book excerpt.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/pixar-president-recalls-a-transformation-undergone-by-apple-co-founder-steve-jobs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 12:35:15 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carriers suggest a big-screen 'iPhone 6' could be a 'very special' success in China</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/carriers-suggest-a-big-screen-iphone-6-could-be-a-very-special-success-in-china</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chinese branded smartphones are performing well in their home country, affecting sales of worldwide leaders Apple and Samsung, but buzz is said to be growing in China among customers who are holding out hope for an iPhone with a larger display.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/carriers-suggest-a-big-screen-iphone-6-could-be-a-very-special-success-in-china</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 09:10:34 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge shuts down Apple motion regarding Samsung's 'misleading' opening statements</title>
      <link>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/judge-shuts-down-apple-motion-regarding-samsungs-misleading-opening-statements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Just hours after Apple filed a motion asking to show evidence of alleged misleading and false statements delivered by Samsung counsel in the companies' second California patent trial, a district court judge late Thursday largely denied the request in a way that could narrow Apple's case moving forward.]]></description>
      <guid>http://appleinsider.com/articles/14/04/04/judge-shuts-down-apple-motion-regarding-samsungs-misleading-opening-statements</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 04:14:18 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
